// APP BACKGROUND COLOR
Ti.UI.setBackgroundColor("#000");

// DATA
var aboutMe = [
	{question: "1. What is your name?", answer: "Sequester McKinney"}, 
	{question: "2. What is your chat user name, including the host?", answer: "quest, Google Hangout"},
	{question: "3. In which time zone do you reside?", answer: "Eastern Standard Time"},
	{question: "4. Why are you in the Mobile Development Program?", answer: "To learn how to create innovative and cutting-edge mobile applications"},
	{question: "5. How comfortable are you with Javascript?", answer: "I am not very comfortable with JavaScript"},
	{question: "6. How comfortable are you with Titanium?", answer: "I am becoming more comfortable with Titanium"},
	{question: "7. What is your favorite food?", answer: "Fried Chicken"},
	{question: "8. What kind of work do you do?", answer: "Web/Infrastructure Developer"},
	{question: "9. WWhat is your favorite movie?", answer: "Captain America: The Winter Solider"},
	{question: "10. Who is your favorite actor/actress?", answer: "Actor: Anthony Hopkins"}
	];

